{"questionlist":[
    {"cardfront":"APP",
    "cardback":"`"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Reset",
    "cardback":"`"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Left Possession",
    "cardback":"1"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Right Possession",
    "cardback":"2"
    },
    {"cardfront": "Before",
    "cardback":"numpad+0"
    },
    {"cardfront":"After",
    "cardback":"numpad+."
    },
    {"cardfront":"That's my point of contact",
    "cardback":"b"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Book it",
    "cardback":"b"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Frame before",
    "cardback":"numpad+0"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Frame after",
    "cardback":"numpad+."
    },
    {"cardfront":"Backwards one bookmark",
    "cardback":"numpad+-"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Forwardwards one bookmark",
    "cardback":"numpad++"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Recall last bookmark",
    "cardback":"numpad++"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Slow",
    "cardback":"numpad+6"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Contact Loop",
    "cardback":"numpad+2"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Intensity Loop",
    "cardback":"numpad+8"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Let's check the APP",
    "cardback":"delete"
    },
    {"cardfront":"Pause",
    "cardback":"numpad+5"
    },
   ]}